Hiii! This is Tuttle. She's joining me for a video today, a transformation video.
I'm going to do a latex makeover with you.
Have you worn latex before?
Just a simple outfit. I have a top and a skirt, but that's it.
So not very much.
Not really.
Okay, we're going to change that today.
Are you okay with me putting you in like a lot of latex?
I guess.
Okay.
That is consent.
So I have a few things planned. So you're usually not doing like latex content obviously, but what do you do?
I think it's cosplay? Yeah, I do like cute little outfits
I upload them on Patreon most of the time, but sometimes just conventions, Instagram. So no cosplay today
we did that in a different video and
Yeah, it's latex time and I'm going to send you upstairs to get changed now
I'll see you in a few minutes
So what I have planned for today is a latex leggings, a bodysuit with fake boobs around 800g, a corset, a neck corset and gloves.
We'll see how she's going to react to that.
Alright, we're back. I'm just finishing up the last touches. How are you doing?
I'm good.
Alright, okay. Then get in front of the mirror and big reveal in a few seconds.
Alright, ready? I guess I am.
That's something new. So what do you think?
It's something new. I don't know what I expected but I don't think... not this but...
Is this good or bad now?
I think I actually like it. I love the corset. It fits you really good.
It's amazing. It feels nice. Yeah.
So we got like really really high boots and the leggings which is 0.25mm.
You've never worn latex leggings before, but getting it in a t-shirt is actually quite okay.
Yeah, it wasn't as hard as I thought.
That's because it's really stretchy and yeah.
And then we have the bodysuit with the big boobs.
How do I feel? I always love how they bounce a little.
It's funny.
And then the corset and neck corset.
I didn't know those were a thing.
It's interesting.
Interesting feeling.
Interesting good or interesting bad?
I'm not sure yet.
That's true.
I have to admit I'm not a huge fan of neck crosshairs either.
But I thought we're going all in.
And I think you look really great.
Definitely something you can pull off.
Maybe turn around for us?
Nice.
Oh god.
Are the boots okay? Yeah. Most of the time I just wear like chunky boots.
They do for festivals and concerts. Yeah. Pointy. But I have like a lot of plateau so they're basically also comfortable.
But it's like they're more comfortable than I expected. Yeah. Because of plateau.
So you know like normal fabric corsets and it's the first time you're
wearing a latinx corset? It's the first time I'm wearing a corset that actually
fits that tight. This is mine. I did that so it's good that it fits you.
Oh wow. Amazing. Looks really great. So good to know that you basically can wear what I wear.
Very good to know. Yeah. You can just steal all your clothes. Would you go to party like that?
I don't think with the boobs. They're a bit too much for me. That's not my usual style but
the leggings, the corset, the gloves. I like it.
Nice.
Well, I can tell you the boobs are getting like a bit heavier after a while.
I can't imagine.
It's like half a kilo, like one and a half kilo in total and yeah.
But it does not look too much, the boobs.
I mean, you're tall, you can pull them off.
Nice! So let's take a selfie but I actually have to go to the other side.
Sorry.
So I can't do it like this.
I snapped a picture of you a few minutes ago and sent it to Fuchs Teufelsville and she
said, well you look good in it.
Oh my.
Oh my!
So if you ever feel like you need something latex-y to wear again, tell me and I might.
I might.
So I hope it didn't scare you away.
No, definitely not.
Cool.
It's really great that you did this with me and trusted me enough.
I mean, I was also wearing cosplay earlier today, so...
You trusted me too!
Did you regret it?
No, I don't. It was pretty fun.
Anyway, let's take some pictures for your pages and then have something to eat.
Please, I'm hungry.
Alright, thanks for joining me today.
You at home, leave a thumbs up and write a comment, check out our socials, I'll link everything in the description text.
thanks for watching this and I'll see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!